is that snow yeah no it's salt let's talk about action free dawn i don't have any shade
i don't nobody should be in prison by this damn um regime wow hi munite i ain't never heard
down let me say shit about palestine now so i'll be kind of reserving my energy
but it definitely is free dawn lemon georgia fort is the only other journalist you said there's
three more damn somebody's joining from bulgaria that's what's up i'm eating spinach goat cheese
quiche that i bought yesterday knowing that we will be on strike today oh hold on i'm sorry geordie
hello honduras you want me to tell it how it is somebody asked did i give up on dating
if dating gave up on me they arrested don lemon because don lemon
is the press and in minneapolis they're using minneapolis as
the next site of the advancement of their repression
and they're really testing the country to see how far folks will go i'm sorry
it's there it's right there get off of here yes i said georgia fort's name
um you know and it's funny because wherever you're at you're wondering well what's it gonna look like
when it gets here and you got to be asking yourself what's your courage look like and when
you say things like how petty the man in the white house is i swear i swear i wish i would really
understand that don that that that donald trump is in it is is not the mass he's not a mastermind
he is the puppet that they make y'all believe is the mastermind so that you think if i just put all
my energy towards him that this will all stop i'm sorry you can get this shirt at cats against genocide
so exactly he's reagan you know he's barely cognizant someone asked me how do i stay sane
um because they're not doing anything that's not not like they're not doing anything out of the
order out of the ordinary i feel like that's when you start going crazy when shit don't make sense
but this shit is you know completely on cue some eugene per year eugene just texted me last night i love
me some eugene per year that's one of the most brilliant people on this planet okay um you know
i really then people ask me like how am i how do i stay happy because i'm a happy bitch i'm a happy
nigga like i'll be i'll be damned if these people gonna make me not happy i mean shit is trash shit
is terrible shit is really horrible but did i get up this morning and do some trampolining i sure did
i got me a mini trampoline for 129 and i got up this morning i know you're not asking me about
tasha k right now the thing about it is that i'll just address your statement tasha k should
never have me in her mouth in her in the first place and the comments that the commentary that
i saw that she had done about me was so mean and that's really what it boils down to it was simply
just mean and you know when people say like it's just my opinion about things that are literally just
you being mean you are adding to the constant flow of oppression that continues to um to suppress us
so she may not have said anything recently mean about me but i recently saw the things that she
has said about me in the past and them them joints was mean as fuck and i don't think that we should be
okay with that i have had to apologize i have had to take accountability i have had to atone
for me falling into the trap of oh it's just content we can't live like that you know like in my play
what would the ancestors say i talk about um you know harriet tubman talks about how the the podcast
bros they just be on the mic saying whatever the fuck not realizing that like when you're on the mic
you are amplified outwardly and inwardly you know what i mean like that that that cord gives you
insight directly into people's you know frequency so you have to be really thoughtful about what you're
doing with that and so many of us have been tricked into thinking that as long as we get in money
that really doesn't matter like the thoughtfulness is really about how to get the money not about what
the results of what we're doing can do to people and i will absolutely tell you that i was a part of
that as well and i had to absolutely check the shit out of myself like amanda what is you doing girl
we all make mistakes it's very easy to be indoctrinated and misled we all are in capitalism
it's incredibly easy to be influenced at some point though you get the you you you can take the
opportunity to say i i was not operating at my highest vibration i was not operating at my best
self at that time and now that i know better i want to do better and commit to that and i think that's
that's something that when someone says that by the way all you can do is just say okay and then see
the actions that's really what atonement is atonement is the actions you know but you you you
and you can announce and say whatever but the atonement is the actions so like when y'all talk
about politicians all the time nobody is actually caring about the actions jasmine jasmine crockett sat
up there and talked all that circuitous nonsense about not being in support of israel and then went and
voted for the next bill that sent weapons to israel like you know i think that a better response from
tasha k would have been you know my bad about those things i really shouldn't have said those things but
that's not the that's not the approach that she took you know and she did send me some voice notes but
in her voice mode she she was essentially defending you know her position and what she thinks about me and
i think it's really important to understand that like unsolicited like having an opinion about
somebody that you don't know i just or that you've never met i think is um really just not it's not
it's not the i don't know how to say it it's just not the way to do it you got some bitch in here
telling me i'm a fool and i'm divisive like you know and i and it's it's it's fascinating
watching y'all say things like that to me because like if you're gonna diss somebody it has to be
accurate for it to be valuable for it to be like an effective diss it gotta be accurate you feel me
so if you're gonna diss me be like you know your parallel parking is not as efficient as it should be
yes like you know i mean like if you're trying to comfort me like hey it needs to be accurate
but like telling me i'm a fool is like telling me i'm ugly like somebody tried to tell me i was ugly
the other day and i was like now you know that's a lie come on now come on now i ain't never been
ugly in my entire fucking life inwardly or outwardly you know telling me i look like a man
then i look like a fine-ass man i might i might post it on my page i don't know i'm really just
trying to keep folks company because i know a lot of us are inside we're on strike we're holding the
line and so as a edutainer i'm just trying to be on here to give y'all something to talk to and
listen to and feel seen and um and you know stand in the gap in that way today so you know that's what
i'm here for i know that i have the gift of charisma so that's how i'm using my gift today
we are all in the process of learning how to fight fascism we should also be in the process of
learning how to be in our bodies and understand our bodies i did an interview this morning with
kelechi okafor who is amazing brilliant lovely and just all the things and she asked me how do i deal
with loneliness and i told her you know to keep it a buck i don't get lonely no more
face card i i mean i fuck with it it's new i'm feeling it out and you know um i said i don't
really get lonely no more because my loneliness was really attributed to a feeling of being misunderstood
and in the last two years i came to really fortify um a uh a strength in myself
but also to understand myself and really like my autism diagnosis really just cleared up a lot of the
shit that had me feeling lonely because i couldn't understand why i couldn't do the certain things
that people wanted me to do and it just felt like like i was just useless because i couldn't do
i couldn't be the person people wanted me to be i couldn't behave the way that people wanted me to
behave like i just couldn't um i couldn't show up that way and it was it was like it just always felt
like i was a failure and it felt very lonely to not be able to understand that and um once i got
clear on the autism it just made me be able to understand and it also began a journey of me being
able to understand that my body is a vessel and like people had said that to me before
but i didn't it didn't really hit and it really hit like oh your body is like a house is the housing
for your soul and your soul is what's like making this brain function the way it does
and you got to protect both and so you got to treat your body different and understanding my
autism taught me how to eat thank you nola taught me how to um treat my body in a way that protects my
soul am i making sense coming on talking about high sexy you get blocked immediately so i've been
really doing so my someone asked about my diagnosis my diagnosis is a self-diagnosis i was um guided
through some tests with my psychiatrist and um i was also i also began doing research
talking to my mom about you know things that i was doing in my youth
and it really cleared up 43 years at the time 43 years um of of um mystery for me about myself
nikki you can look on my page and see my post about miss shirley that has a picture of me and
miss shirley so yes i really wish y'all would actually look at my content sometimes y'all ask me
questions that are so obviously a reflection of the fact that you don't actually look at my content
and it really is annoying to be quite honest because i make a lot of content and i make it just for you
i don't need to make it for me i make it for you people ask me to come back to instagram
and so i did and so i would really like for you all to actually look at my content if you feel
like you haven't seen my videos in a while that's because i'm shadow banned and so you should
go on my page and actually go through and look at the videos that i've made so anywho um the i would
say the biggest thing about the autism diagnosis was literally just the basic like clarity that
my brain works different so i have to operate different that's it that that shifted my entire
understanding of how i live in the world these came in today these came in today i'm gonna put
spinners on the first hundred of them that wasn't la mamba that was jedi what was the most surprising
change that helped you sleep understanding that sleep is don't be scared for me don't ever be scared
for me pray for me lift me up rejoice for me delight for me don't ever be scared for me never
don't ever be scared for me that doesn't help me fear is not a useful tool
you know being be in action for me being supportive me being love be loud of course i'll be why would i
not post more content to scroll up scrolls y'all like yes um someone said but you be up early i go to
bed at 10 30 i wake up at 7 a.m every day and understanding the necessity to sleep
not just because it's the thing you're supposed to do at at night but because it is
literally like putting yourself on a charger
was illuminating for me like i just never really regarded sleep with that much value it was more so
just like this the thing i'm supposed to do but once i was able to really grasp that no i have to
sleep or else i will not be functional in a real way like you know when people would be like oh i don't
want to go out late because i'm gonna be sleepy the next day i never used to understand that because
i'd be like okay so much you sleep you tired the next day big what and it's like no you're not
going to be functional so you might be you might be making mistakes um you know you might be angry
like angie aggie etc and so when that was really implemented i also saw just a complete change in my
mental health that being said i have trained myself to be able to sleep anywhere under any circumstances
because that's how they torture you they give you sleep deprivation so there's a book by paulo
who wrote the alchemist and he also wrote a book called the warrior of light and in the book he says
lack of sleep will have you fighting battles you've already won how do i sleep anywhere i know
how to shut my body down katherine o'hara has passed away to be quite honest anybody who is passing away
right now i'm like good for you get out of here get out of here i'm like congratulations like i've been
on sets for a long time like as an actor right and so what will happen is that you'll be on set but you
may not get to go back to your trailer so you gotta like find a way to get some sleep
um and i mean i can sleep sitting up in a in a room full of people just like this
now i'm not saying it's gonna be rem sleep but it's gonna be sleep um i could sleep on a plane
um and when i was so like also um like being on sets is and also doing stand-up because you know
there'll be times where like my set is until 1 30 a.m so i'm at the club like wake me up when my
when i when i'm about to go on stage so that's a skill that is is something that folks should
really work on how to shut them it's so funny to me when people come into a live and act like the
world started because they got to the live like someone just came in here and said can we get into
this don stuff you just got here how you frame things y'all think about your wording because if
you had said can we come back to this don stuff i would not have called you out i think it's kind
of annoying to me though how surprised y'all be about everything that's when that's that's kind of
irksome to me how surprised y'all be at everything and i'm just like why why why
why is everything so new to y'all um what do you expect is next what do you suspect is next
um what do you suspect is next well i suspect that they will expand what they're doing in
minneapolis to somewhere else you know they don't have the manpower to repress all at once
because the united states is massive so they're just doing city by city the epstein files it's like
it seems like y'all think the epstein files are about donald trump that's not why they're not
releasing the epstein files in my opinion nikki trying to get her pedophile brother out of prison
i mean i understand it's your sibling but you know we got to be able to acknowledge like
when people we love are harmful people well i think they well first of all they didn't target
minneapolis first right they targeted los angeles and dc and chicago they were in north carolina
um they were in portland so they they were in they're in new york so they didn't start
with minneapolis they escalated in minneapolis they was in new orleans now minneapolis is a
very like minneapolis well minnesota has like a lot of social programs and also it has um a history
of being you know unified in rabble rousing don't ever forget george floyd was in minneapolis
they burnt down the precinct y'all then people ain't for play so i think they were like okay
we know that if we go here we can um turn up and we'll be met with turn up and they want
an opportunity to to attempt to put in martial law i think a total shutdown is the only option
who is justin la boy and why are you so grossed out that they're in this chat i don't think we have
the willpower in this country i think we have a very romanticized view of um how other countries
operate i think we see a protest in other countries and we think well look what they can do a lot of
times we don't even know what they're protesting and i think there are some examples that are very
clear in like okay this is a country whose culture protests which is korea um brasil
but you know when people are saying like you know folks are lazy folks aren't willing to let go of
the conveniences etc etc well they're gonna be taken from us all these conveniences y'all talk
about they're gonna be taken from us and the truth of the matter is white people you know y'all's
people don't really y'all ain't really the best at doing work so the quality of everything about to go
down hey val hey arena so but we have been tricked into thinking that like certain positions are for
smart people and other positions are not for smart people and it's like slaves who had
no capability to be allowed to read slaves who had no capability to even like have control over their
bodies managed to create managed to sow plant and sow crops okay they managed to plant and sow crops
on land that they didn't even know that's expertise like that's skill so like you know this whole thing
of like unskilled workers and shit like that you know who the most unskilled workers are in this
nation in my opinion politicians and cops politicians and cops are the most unskilled workers they don't
do the job that they're supposed to do well and they don't do and they don't do the job they're
pretending to do well so do not like lie to yourself and think well you know
them people are more better than me etc etc no they not no they not you better get you some friends and
know how to farm but know how to grow shit now me i'm a nigga that be figuring it out i have the gift of
figuring it out i know just enough about pretty much everything to get me across somewhat of a finish line
okay thank you lynn sanity hi amanda they're saying they're trying to say he was disruptive to
operations who don lemon of course he was disruptive to operations he's supposed to be he's a police he
is the he is a reporter and when you're trying to do shady shit you're exposing that you're disruptive
to operations journalists into resa that's why they systematically murdered the journalists that
were in resa already because they're palestinian but they didn't allow outside journalists into resa
i have no idea what's happening with the fdic right now you're exhausted i see so many white and
bipod folks posting katherine o'hara and not don lemon girl use your energy for something else that that
can't be the thing that exhausts you what people are posting on the internet cannot be the thing
that exhausted you that exhausts you i mean that's mrs mccallister that's a part of an entire
generation's nostalgia like they gonna post her fridays are not slow news days fridays are never slow
news days with this administration they literally do everything on fridays because they don't want the
news to cover it on saturday and sunday the f-team files are about holding power they're not about
don they're not really about donald trump they're about holding power they're about the folks who
who really are exerting power over the world and this was a method that they used to keep a certain
tier of individuals in check to carry out their wishes it's that's what it's about so no we're never
gonna see the quote-unquote epstein files and to be quite honest it wouldn't matter at this point i
realized it wouldn't matter unless it made folks say fuck this shit we burning it down that's the only
reason why it would matter that's right just moseying along no credit card transactions no gas
purchases no work no shopping today shout out to everybody who kept their kids home from school
shout out to everybody who used a sick day today who you know really said okay i'm gonna be a part of
this shutdown today if they were able to we commend you thank you i don't think that's why they aren't
releasing it i think they aren't releasing it because it's still something they can hold over people's
heads whitney cummings went off on miss rachel whitney cummings went off on miss rachel what whitney
cummings went off on in what context tatiana epstein oh my god you guys if you can name the person
they're not in charge okay if you can name the person they're not in charge epstein was not in
charge he was an asset carrying out the will of a greater force you don't know who those people are
and that's the work that needs to happen is those people need to be uncovered and they need to be
brought out we need to bring the light to the shadows once and for all which we have not been
able to do in 400 years and then you all say things like we're never gonna and it just it gets my goat
every time because so many um someone just said i don't give a fuck i don't know who the hell y'all be
thinking you're talking to i really don't i really don't i don't give a fuck start with the who are you
talking to who are you talking to um the people at the very top are not black that's for sure and uh
also it's not to say that you don't acknowledge you don't call out the people that you do see and
that you don't you know use them to get to what you don't see however it it's so often presented as
if that's the that's the pinnacle hey anthony when did you hear that when did you hear we're not
supposed to go on live today when when was that the rule well it's already three o'clock
so i'm gonna go work on some music wishing you all the best on this day
hope that you can take the time out to be still to ask yourself not everything is some kind of
mysterious demon in the shadows blocked yes it is yes it is everything that we are suffering from
right now is being carried out by demons who live in the shadows and the sooner you all stop believing
that you know things that you don't know the quicker we will get to the revealing
of that which we need to know any of us who have the level of ego to say such and such is not such and
such when we have nothing based on like it like it's beyond my scope of comprehension that anyone could
say is that anyone could say everything isn't because you don't you there's no reason for you to know
that that's not the case you've never been told the truth ever you have never been told the truth
so at this juncture we should all be open to the possibility of everything aliens maybe
demons in the shadows perhaps we've never been told the truth so it would behoove you
to um suspend your disbelief because you were only given the parameters of your belief
by the folks who don't want you to consider the possibilities all right i want you to think about
that your concept of freedom was given to you your concept of crazy was given to you
your concept of success was given to you your concept of life and death was given to you
how much of those things did you ever consider for yourself how many of those things did you ever sit
and decide what is my version of this in some cases probably none it was just decided for you and you
accepted it and we are now in an era where we cannot simply be an accepting body we need to be confronting
everything that comes across our path that's why we have to be in community that's why i have to be
for fortifying our bodies that's why we have to be drug free that's why we have to do everything
in our possibility to access the bit we have to do everything in our capability to access the highest
level of our capabilities because they are counting on you not to be able to so anytime someone tells you
well it could be stop yourself if you find yourself saying nah why not and your why not nine times out of
10 is going to come from a concept that was given to you you don't even know where it came from aliens
aren't real why you heard what i said what do you mean we have to be drug free you heard what i said
we really need to be able to get to a point where we are not taking these people's narcotics
i didn't stutter drinking these people alcohol all this shit is poison all of it you think i want to be
on lexapro i don't want to be on lexapro because i'm in these people's synthetic fucking world and so
now i gotta take their synthetic medication to manage their synthetic fucking world even the
weed y'all smoking did you grow it because some of that weed y'all smoking baby that shit is from
saturn from jupiter the cheese we eat this shit is addictive like this is not just i'm not just and
i'm not saying it to you i'm saying it to me i'm saying it to us like this is literally this drink right
here was um apple juice from a farm okay apple juice from a farm strawberries and um kale
and
seagrass from grenada and i couldn't get the seagrass to be like a gel consistency like i soaked it i put
it in the food processor and i couldn't get it to be like um a gel consistency so that meant that like
even when i blended it i still like was chewing it and at first i was like damn
i don't know if i like this and then i and then i said to myself amanda you are literally eating
the ocean like you're eating the gift of the ocean sea moss is a gift from the ocean
so like chew that shit up chew this sea moss up and eat it as for weed smoke your weed like i said
like i mean we're we're just trying to figure out how to get through this time so do what you gotta do
just know the goal is for us to not have to do things to get through have a good day
val that with the sea moss you can't like some people be like eating sea moss like by itself and
it's like that's crazy um i have to like put it in a in a um in a uh slushy or like i like in a
in a smoothie normally i get it in a gel form and when it's in the smoothie you don't notice at all
but i couldn't do that and the lady in the market gave me some free sea moss when i was in grenada so i
was like well this came right from the ocean righty so i have to use it i have to use it
and so um there you go